

Frontend Developer Ha Noi, Vietnam

giahung197bg@gmail.com









## About

Hi, my name is Hung, i'm 26 years old. I got a bachelor of Electronics Telecommunication Engineering at Ha Noi University of Science and Technology. Besides, i am really passionate about Javascript and Web Development.

I am also an open-source enthusiast and maintainer. I love how collaboration and knowledge sharing happens through open-source and I am happy to see what I do could eventually feedback to the community and industry.

## **Work Experience**

#### AgileTech Vietnam Frontend Developer

Dec 2020 - Present | Nhân Hòa, quận Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the projects of the company.
- Training new members of the company.

## Beau Agency Vietnam Frontend Developer Intern

Dec 2019 - Dec 2020 | Hoàng Văn Thái, Thanh Xuân, Hà Nội

- Worked on developing and maintaining the company's e-commerce, landing page website
- Developed and maintained the project on shopify platform.

## **Projects**

## NXB 7

Management book and national newspaper

## Pinex <sup>↗</sup>

Finance social network

## Maby <sup>↗</sup>

Book an appointment, Search for the nearest salon, Search for a salon by city, View details of the salon, Notification function when there is a new appointment, cancel an appointment

#### Gourmet Market Thailand 7

Building a sales website, Manage orders, Order function, Order management, product review, Order payment by visa/mastercard

#### XO Sections 7

XO Sections is a great solution with tons of customizing options

### Mathpang 7

Learn math online for elementary school students.

## Hillridge <sup>↗</sup>

Agricultural construction insurance

## Maby Salon <sup>→</sup>

Book an appointment, Manage an appointment, View details of the salon, Notification function when there is a new appointment, cancel an appointment

#### Summoners Arena 7

Building a website to buy and sell heroes with tokens, Exchange tokens, Create and manage events



# Open Source Software

Svg To Icon 🗘 🗷	CSS To Tailwindcss 🧿 🗷
Convert svg to icon	Convert css to tailwindcss
★ 5	<b>★</b> 7
Quillis Resize Image O 7	CSV Parser O 7
A module resize image for quilljs	A module parse csv file for nodejs
<b>★</b> 10	<b>★</b> 7
React Sticky O 7	React OTP Input O 7
A library sticky element for reactjs	A library otp input for reactjs
<b>★</b> 6	<b>★</b> 9
More Projects	
Stacks  Front and LITML CCC Type Covint love Covint Depoties	Nortia Daminia Vita Cualta Mahmada
Frontend HTML, CSS, TypeScript, JavaScript, Reactjs, Nextjs, Remixjs, Vite, Svelte, Webpack  Backend Nodejs, Nestjs, MongoDB, PostgreSQL	
DevOps Firebase, Nginx, Docker, CI/CD	
Languages C/C++	
Education	
<b>Electronics Telecommunication Engineering, Engineer</b> , Hanoi university of science and technology Sep 2015 - Sep 2020	
Interests	
Reading	
Coding	
References	
Nguyen Manh Thang	
CEO at Agiletech Vietnam	
Nguyen Hoai Nam	
Techlead at Agiletech Vietnam	
Neo Khuat	
CTO at Beau Agency Vietnam	

## Vietnamese (Native speaker), English (Beginner)

# Online Version

Last updated at January 23rd 2024, 11:38:41 am